I carry high my craven flag,
my ally I'm gonna fly and let my
struggles shoot me through the sky!
It'd be a pity if we
lingered here and let our
pretty sparks of life
blend aloud and disappear?
There may be fog that even
you can't navigate If someone
strong like you is lost then
who will set me straight?
Cause when the waves
cast, my heart exists?
It's been your kindness and your strength!
That would free me from the mist.
And just like that!
We move on.
Sail to a new dawn.
Weigh anchor, ride as high as you can!
I assure I don't need anger.
I go fast as I am, yeah.
I hear you laughing like
you're numb to it all?
Well, we're dashing together!
No, we're never gonna fall, you know!
The whole world may now be my enemy?
Water swirl, but I ain't backing
down so long as I'm free!
Thought I'll give it, come
round the current with me.
All in, wake up bright and
early, making for the peak we go!
How dare they publish this?
I'm with that picture, no less. Absurd.
We told you to remove
the D and you ignored us.
We weren't informed, I swear.
We got the pictures from Tang of CP0.
We just thought...
Reprint them immediately.
Do you hear me?
We can't let this trash get out.
I'm sorry, sir!
We can't contact the printing company!
Useless idiots!
Stop them, or you'll all pay the price!
That photo really excites
the imagination, doesn't it?
Keep it up, everyone!
We'll deliver every last copy!
Cipher Pole infiltrated the land of water,
and no one's heard a peep from them since!
In their last transmission, they
said Big Mop's ship had arrived.
The government won't
manipulate this story.
Not on my watch!
When the winds of change are whipping
up a storm, nothing beats the truth.
The news never stops!
It's flying full speed!
Whoa, what's this?
A special report? What happened?
Oh wow, check this out!
Emperors of the sea Kaido and Big
Mom defeated news this massive could
not be contained and It spread across
the world like wildfire the people
were clamoring to learn the names of
The three pirate captains who ended
the emperor's reign and the world
government was swift in their Judgment,
placing an exorbitant bounty on each head.
Three billion berries?
Wow, boss. Nice, Captain.
Let me see.
I have got to look at this up close.
Check this part out.
Holy crap.
Hey, boss, where are you going?
He's even Pizarro than usual.
What do you think he's running off to?
The flower capital, I'm sure.
We have a new emperor
of the sea, after all.
And it's no surprise who it is.
Hey, guys.
I heard there's a banquet
in the capital today.
Let's go tear it up.
Just in time for us to celebrate.
I'm about to let loose, baby. Yeah!
It's festival time!
We're ready to party!
This is going to be a disaster, I know it.
Add cloudier mushrooms and chrysanthemum
leaves, a plate of Geoise tofu,
some flower-shaped lotus
roots, next up, cucumber salad.
We must not let any harm
befall our honored guests.
Grind everything once,
heat it up and reshape it?
then test it for poison three times.
I've honed these skills over decades,
all in service of this wondrous day.
Traditional cuisine fit for a shogun!
Please enjoy!
What is this?
Where is everyone?
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
A rowdy crew won't wait two hours
for food, no matter how tasty.
A pity, since this is
quite the sight to behold.
You've done splendid work, Chef.
Hm?
It sounds like the festival's starting.
Party time! Party time!
Let's grab that food and go!
Chocolate bananas!
Fried noodles!
Octopus balls!
Wow, squid!
That's candy, too!
This is the greatest!
That festival?
Everything's free!
Totally free!
My very first festival!
This is so fun!
I can't decide what I want to eat next!
There's just so much
awesome-looking stuff, you know?
Hey, look over there! What are those?
They're called candy apples!
You eat it?
It looks like a jewel!
Beautiful!
It's sweet and sour and delicious.
Fruit is good, but candy
fruit is a dream come true.
Okay, less talking, more eating, Chopper.
Now that's tasty!
There's stalls with games
and stuff too, right?
Since you guys are the festival
experts, can you show me some?
No, bro, follow me.
Once you've had all the food, there's
one thing you always gotta try!
Right now! Gum-Gum! Target! Shoot it!
I never miss!
I don't think that's how you play!
Yeah, Luffy, you can't use your hand!
Oh, okay!
Can I try again?
I broke the net!
You're up next!
Don't worry, I'll show you how it's done!
Two in one stroke!
Wow, you're a real pro!
Oh, I wish I was as good as you!
That sweet time doesn't
make me happy, you bastards!
Looks pretty happy to me!
All right, Wano!
You wanna rock?
Hey, it's Brook!
Knock him down, Brook! Yeah!
I'd like to introduce you
all to my jam partner!
Wano's Pitch Perfect Princess!
Cause if you rock with the Soul
King, then you gotta be royalty!
That's right!
We're serving up Brother
Omer's favorite tune!
Moon Princess!
Princess Yachty!
What are these?
Find something of interest. Nico Robin.
Mr. Tang.
You know my name?
What do you think of my treasure?
What aren't they cute?
They're fine.
I struck a nerve.
You're funny. Mr. Tang.
By the way, this is a rather odd
place for your collection. Isn't it?
I do hope you realize I was joking.
I suppose you might call
this my secret hobby room,
and I was also confined
here for quite some time.
Confined?
It seems you're more
than just a swordsmith.
Yes, it's but a pastime.
Seems I have a good
aptitude for it, though.
I never cared for
festivals during my reign.
Wait, who are you really?
Ah, well...
I am the father of Kozuki Oden.
My name is Kozuki Sukiyaki.
The Shogun?
Does Momo know you're alive?
He doesn't.
And I'll keep it that way.
But I have a feeling my son's retainers
have figured out who I am by now.
At any rate, I'm the one responsible
for the tragedy that befell this land.
I'm too ashamed to tell
anyone that I'm alive.
When I emerged from this room,
barely clinging to life, Odin was
dead and my beloved home was in ruins.
I felt such remorse.
I thought to slip my belly on the spot.
Still, I had no choice but to hide.
I had a mission to carry out.
I could not fail my country again.
But now,
the land of Wano is free,
and for that I owe my deepest
gratitude to you and your friends.
Well, I think they'd be very happy
if you told them that in person.
I see.
That aside, there's something
else I need to ask you about.
I've been informed that this
country has an ancient weapon.
Pluton.
How did you know that it's written on
the poneglyph in the kingdom of Alabasta?
I never imagined you'd know of
such a thing but yes it's here!
Oh, I've got my voluptuous car!
You don't know when to quit!
You guys aren't even captains.
If I lose to you, I'll
be a walking discreet!
This is a damn mess, and the Navy
doesn't have the manpower to clean it up.
But it looks like you were
worth fighting after all.
Wouldn't want you to
start in trouble later.
This is weak booze if I've ever tasted it.
Should have expected that from
a weak-ass crew like yours.
Hello?
This is...
Listen, it's me.
Send a warship to the land
of Wano. What? Real kugyu?
And don't squeal the sakazuki
either, got it? Kullik.
No offense, boss.
I still like you.
Especially the way you never cut corners.
If I break some rules,
I know you won't mind.
Because I'm bringing you this kid's head.
Look, up there! Who is that?
Time for a toast, I see!
Is he going to make a speech?
Ninja's pirates, minx, and samurai!
The shogun's retainers!
Yakuza and the people of Wano!
You guys really kicked some ass out there!
You said it, pal!
Whoever you are!
I'll drink to that!
This guy's the king of the banquet! Yeah!
I'm king of the banquet!
Muffy.
Don't tell the land of
Wano about me, okay?
What? Why not?
Because it'd make me a hero.
And what's wrong with that?
You're the one who defeated Kaido.
The people need to know.
Don't be dumb.
Wano has been waiting
for you, Momo, not me.
Get out of my body!
Hey, straw hatch! Huh?
I'm taking you out right now! Taggy!
Fireworks ready? Let's go!
A toast to good food every single day!
What the hell?
I'll kill you!
Here we go!
Cheers!
Yeah!
It's time to show them how to party!
Hmm, perhaps another bottle is in order.
Time for a feast!
Empty those cups and fill them up again!
Don't stop till dawn!
Pirates know how to
celebrate, I'll say that much.
In all my futures, I've never
been to a banquet like this.
Listen, this victory, this moment shared
with friends, will stay with me forever.
I'm not here to have a
toast with you, damn it!
And why come to the
party in the first place?
Guess you haven't been keeping
up with the news overseas, huh?
Here, see this?
I'm gonna take you out
while I still have a shot!
Wado?!
The news that shocked the world came
as quite a surprise to Luffy as well.
It was a moment that marked the end of the
old regime and the beginning of a new era.
A shift in power left four
influential pirates in the spotlight.
Buggy the Genius Jester.
Blackbeard Teach.
Redhead Shanks.
And after his victory, Straw Hat Luthu.
The four of you are the
new emperors of the sea!
Sounds like they're having a lot of fun.
But the Navy didn't come here to
dance to your tour, little shit!
The party's over.
I'm gonna bleed all of you dry.
You've turned the whole
damn world upside down.
So I'll be taking your head
as means of an apology.
Rahahahaha!
It's been a while, huh?
I haven't seen this country
since I bid farewell to Odin.
Momo and Hiyori must
be all grown up by now.
Someone is here.
And they're sneaking into Wano.
Is something wrong, ma 'am?
Such a foreboding presence.
Something's out there.
Shinobu!
You felt it too?
I know not what it is,
but it draws closer.
Everyone, listen.
Sir Luffy and the others are still
recovering from their battle injuries.
We can't let them know about this.
So Yuka are noticed too, I see.
Do not let the sounds
of the festival stop.
Let us go!
The thing about influence is,
when you want it,
it just slips away.
Hey I only have business
with Straw Hat Luffy so
Why don't you just step
aside samurai he's a
marine they've come for
Sir Luffy they're the
Enemy of pirates but how did one get here
interesting so you know
about the outside world
Well I can still teach you a thing or two
Come on
Kappa style!
River of Retribution!
What a pain.
What?
You're testing my patience.
Stand down!
The celestial dragons are
the gods of the world.
And since the land of Wano chooses
to live outside their rule?
Its people have no rights.
Thank you.
Race, we can't let him go!
Groves of wrath.
I have the power of the
woods-woods fruit, a woodsman!
The forest is the cradle of life.
Just like the sea, it's
the very essence of Logia.
Get in my way!
And I can kill you all
without a second thought.
The government doesn't protect you
because to the rest of the world,
you're not human.
What did you say?
How dare you speak that
way about our people?
Mankind has always divided itself
and chosen who to label as inferior.
You can think of it this way.
The sacrifice of the few is what
guarantees the peace of the many
Unaffiliated countries like yours have
no choice but to accept your suffering.
When the rest of the world looks down on
you, it reaffirms their worth as humans!
Discrimination creates comfort.
Don't blame me!
This is how the world works!
Try and stop me!
You're dead!
I'll kill thousands of
you insects if that's
what it takes to get destroyed on Luffy!
Everything you say is disgusting!
I've heard enough out of you!
Hey, what's the hold-up?
Let's go see Luffy.
He's come far enough, hasn't he?
He's one hell of a pirate.
He really did it, huh?
That's strong Haki.
This country has suffered for 20 years.
On this day, they celebrate a freedom
they fought tooth and nail for.
I won't let you spoil it.
And who the hell are you?
I'm Yamato.
I'm the son of Kaido.
He has a child.
Well spoken, my friend.
Lord Momonosuke.
The heroes who saved this
country deserve their rest.
I will make certain they
have it. The dragon?
Black breath!
Be careful, my lord!
No matter!
If you must fight, do it
away from the capital!
You will not trouble my people!
I made a promise to
them and I will keep it!
A pink dragon?
I've never heard of a devil
fruit power like that.
That's it!
Yamato, please, step
back from this battle!
We should be coming up on water real soon!
Wait!
We can't land there.
I'm sorry, but I'm just
not ready to see Usopp.
Yeah, bet that little bastard
kid is still there, too.
He picked a fight with us once.
I'm sure he'll do it again.
Relax, would you?
Leave it to the boss.
There's no point in fighting over it.
That power...
you're kidding that's
red-haired shanks they've
got some Cape agents on
board huh what a pain
don't worry let's go
FIRE!
WE NEED TO HOLD STREETS BACK!
Dammit!
Why would they be targeting us?
What do they want?
We're not carrying any treasure with us!
All we have is a Devil Fruit.
Do they want stupid
rubber powers that bad?
You better start taking me seriously.
I'll prove how tough I am.
Yeah?
Let's see.
You idiot!
What are you doing?
Hold on a sec, Luffy. Come back.
What's going on here?
I'm stretchy!
What the heck?!
Get lost.
Oh, come on. Stop crying.
You're a man, right?
But, Jinx, your arm!
Your arm!
Guess all the top guys know Straw
Hat Luffy from back in the day.
What kind of pirate do you think he is?
I've heard Straw Hat luffy
is totally out of control!
He's a violent monster like
an ape in human clothing!
Come on, boss?
We're gonna go, aren't we?
I don't need to see Luffy yet.
Besides, think about what's
been going on in our territory?
You're talking about our Jolly
Roger getting burned, right?
What was that guy's name?
He said he was Luffy's underling
and replaced our flag with his Mr.
Luffy's gonna be king of the pirates
Take this free sticker to support him.
But this is Shanks' territory,
and he's an emperor of the sea.
Screw that!
I don't care about no damn emperor!
I have a reputation to uphold.
Can't just let it slide.
Okay, sure, that's one way to look at it.
But on the other hand, we'd
just be saying hi to a friend.
We can't let the Revolutionary Army
get away with this anymore, Akahinu.
I'd love to stomp them out, but we
don't have enough troops to deploy.
Sabo.
He's become their hero, and
now the whole world knows.
Nefertari Cobra was the sole king
at the Reverie descended from
the first 20 who created the
world government 800 years ago.
As far as symbolic victories go,
I don't think the Revolutionary Army
could have asked for a better outcome.
Hours before the assassination,
in the land of the gods where
the world nobles reside,
the Revolutionaries declared war by
destroying the hoof of the Celestial Dragon,
a symbol of divine rulership.
Admirals Ryokugyu and Fujitora
led the Navy forces into battle,
but the enemy escaped.
And then, they freed the former
revolutionary Bartholomew Kuma,
who had been enslaved by
the Celestial Dragons.
Hmm, a stunning loss.
Must have been hard for the admirals
to fight in the land of the gods.
Let's not make excuses
for them, they failed.
The report says Princess
Vivi is nowhere to be found.
Went poof, around the same
time as her father's murder.
Not sure if the two cases are related.
I'll look into it.
Alabasta must be hurting right now.
King Cobra's ship is still
sitting at the Red Port.
They can't even send it home
thanks to all the madness going on.
What about the attempted murder of St.
Charles?
Are we closing the case on that one?
Well, St.
Miosgaard has been accused of
letting the assailant escape.
They're deliberating over the
matter in the land of the gods.
The Holy Knights have intervened
and it's turned into a huge mess.
Not our problem let them
figure it out in each
case the public is
convinced that Sabo was the
one pulling the strings
this caused quite a
stir as you might guess
he's a popular man in the
lands that were part of the eight nation
revolution sparks of rebellion
of starting fires all
over the world and to the
traders Sabo is a hero
they worship him like
some kind of god they've
even started calling him
the flame emperor he's
become so popular he's
even overshadowed the
revolutionary army's leader
the insurgent serpent
dragon on top of all that
Sabo's little brother
is Straw Hat Luffy how
cute they're both emperors
the flame emperor will strike down the old
regime just like his
brother did in the world
of pirates this is the
beginning of a new era
What a mess picked a hell of
a time to be fleet admiral
Fine you bastards can
do your worst I won't
lose no matter how many of you come at me
Let's go.
Well, Beck, it's time.
I think we're ready to go for it.
The One Piece.